(Leonard:)Yeah, it's a perfectly good word.
I mean, you put it in front of "dokay"
and you really got something.
All right, let's not overreact.
(Penny:)It takes time
to get to know each other's rhythms.
(Penny:)Learn what the other person wants
and likes.
(Leonard:)-So you've been through this before?
-No.
(Leonard:)Okay-dokay.
(Penny:)This is one of those things where talking
about it is not gonna make it better.
-Want a glass of wine? Okay.
-So much.
(Penny:)See, we should've done this last night,
you know?
Had a little wine, take the edge off.
(Leonard:)Actually, ethyl alcohol inhibits
electrical conduction in the nerve cells...
(Leonard:)...and stimulates reuptake receptors
of inhibitory neurotransmitters...
(Leonard:)...like gamma-aminobutyric acid.
(Penny:)Don't talk. Just drink.
(Howard:)No, you're misunderstanding.
(Howard:)A shiksa goddess
isn't an actual goddess.